<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Bala</title>
    <link>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Bala</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bala.netlify.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/littleluxuries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/littleluxuries/</guid>
      <description>I belong to a middle class family - our dreams are usually driven by a budget marked with upgraded eras. We got a black and white television in the early 90s - invitations to a community binge watch session for Ramayana on Sundays were a thing then. Then we got a scooter somewhere in the late 90s and finally, my family could travel together on the two wheeler adjusting babies in between my parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo?</title>
      <link>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/metoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/metoo/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a webpage when the train came whistling to the platform. I stood up sliding forth my trolley, and took a moment to move it to the raised train bogie. Just two hours and I&amp;rsquo;ll be home! &amp;lsquo;Jaldi chadhiye madam. Nahi to aapka pani hum pee lenge.’
It took me a moment to decipher that it didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything to do with the gravity working on my green bottle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failure Stories</title>
      <link>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/failurestories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/failurestories/</guid>
      <description>At the age of ten, I wanted to be the God - you know the supreme powerful lord of the universe, who gets a house up in the sky, unlimited amenities with some of my favourite eatables as offerings - and of course, the power to control my one crazy not so little family!
In those days, I was doing academically well. I topped my class, cracked inter-school competitions and delivered good oratory experiences - I was the golden child at my high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Father and Reverse Parenthood</title>
      <link>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/offather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/offather/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t have it in me to look him in the eye and say these three golden words - Happy Father&amp;rsquo;s Day, Pappa! We don&amp;rsquo;t share that kind of relationship anymore.
I miss the good old days - I could lay across your chest in the whitest of underpants listening to your Kauwa and Maina - none of them be evil to emphasize on the moral - you&amp;rsquo;d always fall asleep in the middle and we&amp;rsquo;d never reach the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lady Downstairs…</title>
      <link>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/theladydownstairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bala.netlify.com/blog/theladydownstairs/</guid>
      <description>And we met on the stairs - barely registering her presence, I moved my trolley upstairs to shift in this new place in a city I had rarely been to before. I hadn’t told my parents, very few friends knew where I was headed to and even fewer knew about my plans of quitting DU. That one fine day, I had woken up to myself in a tiny room at North Campus to realise that it didn’t make sense to me anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>